[
  {
    "question": "How to buy a name at a discount?",
    "answer": "All current discounts are listed on the main site. If you want to buy the name at a discount, add the desired name to the basket and pay for it."
  },
  {
    "question": "Payment does not pass. What to do?",
    "answer": "Write to us in support if the payment from the bank has passed correctly. For transactional issues, please contact your bank."
  },
  {
    "question": "I can not log into my account",
    "answer": "Try resetting your password. If you have forgotten your email, please enter your phone number when logging in."
  },
  {
    "question": "My card was withdrawn for unknown purchases",
    "answer": "Write to us in support with the exact date of withdrawal of funds from your card."
  },
  {
    "question": "You do not have a name in the store that I want to buy",
    "answer": "All new games are added to our store as soon as we contact the supplier. It takes some time."
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to see the full purchase history",
    "answer": "You can view the purchase history through your personal account."
  },
  {
    "question": "Lost the name of shopping",
    "answer": "Write to us in support of the name of the name and your email at registration."
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to make a gift to a friend",
    "answer": "Unfortunately, we have not yet implemented gifts. Soon this functionality will definitely appear."
  },
  {
    "question": "When I log in to the name, I get an error with the connection",
    "answer": "Check your internet connection. If the error persists, contact the service provider."
  },
  {
    "question": "I paid for the purchase, but the name is not yet available",
    "answer": "Write to us in support of your order number and the time of the transaction."
  }
]
